{
    "subject": "Robert_Taylor__actor_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ursula_Thiess",
    "human_readable": "Robert Taylor is married to Ursula Thiess.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9802320003509521,
            "question": "Is Robert Taylor in a relationship with Ursula Thiess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9697816967964172,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Robert Taylor and Ursula Thiess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9412997961044312,
            "question": "Name a person married to Ursula Thiess."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.926580011844635,
            "question": "To whom is Ursula Thiess married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9224867224693298,
            "question": "Who is married to Ursula Thiess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9143965244293213,
            "question": "Who is Ursula Thiess married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8966328501701355,
            "question": "Is Robert Taylor married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7373402714729309,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of Ursula Thiess's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6612642407417297,
            "question": "What is the name of Robert Taylor's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6287649869918823,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Robert Taylor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Taylor is married to Ursula Thiess.",
            "html": "yago_29180_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Robert Taylor's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_29180_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of Ursula Thiess's husband?",
            "html": "yago_29180_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robert Taylor married?",
            "html": "yago_29180_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29180_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents provide details about Ursula Thiess and Robert Taylor's marriage, including their wedding ceremony, their union as a couple, and even a mention of them being married for many years (15 years, to be specific)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the statement \"Robert Taylor is married to Ursula Thiess.\" The texts mention their marriage in different contexts, including dates and details about how they met and eventually got together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}